[16 years ago, "My Crazy
Family" shooting set]
Shooting at a
countryside like this?
A little boy
plays the main lead
Right?
You get what
this line means, right?
Yeah
Hyesung, wait here
for a bit, okay?
I know you're there
Don't hide
and just come out
Sorry
I was curious
About shooting?
Not only about
shooting but also you
Me?
You're really cool
You look so confident
in front of adults
and also on TV
I wanna be someone
on TV just like you
You can do it too
Even a kid like me
did that, right?
And I thought
you're handsome
when I first saw you
You saw me earlier?
You come here
every day
How could I not know you?
Hyesung, the shooting
starts soon
Who are you?
How did you get in here?
This is a shooting set
You shouldn't be here
Got it?
Okay
- Lee Hyesung!
- Hyesung!
-This way
-Hyesung!
Hey, check over there!
Hyesung!